Mojo Mojo Mojo Spy
Look with your heart, truly look
You'll find the truth is not far away
Hey you good or bad, real or fake
You can't escape this gray haze of the mind
Bring all the courage you've got
Maybe you can save the world
Mojo Mojo Mojo Spy
Mojo Spy
Tomorrow night, you must get the Keys of Hope. Don't let me down. Sender: Blue Cross
Episode 2: Carnival Terror Attack Case, Part 2
Locky!
Locky
Starting today, except for school hours
No going out for a week
The celebration tonight
You're disqualified from attending, too
That face won't help you
Jingjing
Keep an eye on him for me
Make him go home right away
Yes Sir
What do we do? What do we do?
Mr. Mayor
I have a way.
My name is Chivas.
This has been passed down in my family
for ninety-nine generations—a magical clockwork spring.
Toys wound up with it are incredibly strong.
Almost as if they're alive.
Repair the statue.
So easy
Then please start right away.
Gladly.
But I have one condition.
Yes, yes.
No need to be polite.
Out with it.
I've always loved a big occasion, ever since I was a kid.
Could you, during the celebration,
let me have the best spot at the ceremony?
That's easy enough.
I'll arrange the best spot for you.
Right under the statue.
At the very front of the control platform,
dead center.
Deal.
Begin, Seagram.
The plan is going smoothly. Recipient: Blue Cross
My uncle must be hiding something from me
Whenever he lies, he strokes his beard
Oh, right, I'll go find him
My uncle's always got something going on
So I'll go to him first
On second thought, never mind
See that?
It's that kid
He broke the wire at the celebration
Don't cry, Locky
Locky's the best!
I'm not great at all
Curly, leave me alone
I've tried so hard to be a detective
And I'm still that
kid nobody likes
From this cartoon's first season
Episode one until now
Nothing has changed
With you
we can blackmail that kid detective
and get the boss released
Chickenix
This guy definitely went off somewhere to find food.
Xiaoyu, don't you remember me?
That person is...
Stop! Don't run!
Big sis, you saved Chickenix!
Thank you for saving my pet.
I'm Detective Locky.
May I ask your name?
Ya... Yayue.
You... you're Locky.
Whoa, is my name really that scary?
Juice!
Where?
Locky, you liar!
Coral Reef Garden.
This is where Dorothy's trail was found.
Yes.
Uncle really was hiding something from me.
Alright.
Let this great detective investigate thoroughly.
The door lock has been broken.
Soil analysis results.
Nitrate
Magnesium
Aluminum
Sulfur
The carbon proportion
is 60% higher than normal
So much fertilizer
No wonder the plants grow so lush
Wait
Nitrate, sulfur, carbon
Computer
Analyze according to the ratios in the soil
Find the chemical substance with the closest ratio
Could the people here
because they leaked information
have already been dealt with by The Illumin-Eye...
Something's wrong with the ground
Hawxing
Quick, look here
The soil chemical composition comparison results are out
Its similarity ratio to gunpowder composition
is nearly 90%
Oh no
On Celebration Night
The Illumin-Eye
will send you a 'blazing' gift
A blazing gift
Blazing
It might be explosives.
But I checked.
The nearby gunpowder and fireworks factories
haven't lost any raw materials.
Also,
there's one more thing I don't get.
What is it?
Why would Dorothy
deliberately use her real name?
Isn't she afraid the two old folks will call the police?
Uncle!
We've been had!
What?
Yes, Detective Chen.
The garden's owner was an impostor.
Dorothy used
fertilizer containing
chemical components similar to explosives—
ammonium nitrate,
potassium nitrate fertilizer.
This gunpowder was hidden in the soil of the Coral Reef Garden.
Now the explosives have already been dug out.
Damn!
They actually committed the crime right under our noses.
Hawxing, hurry and bring Locky back.
We must ensure the safety of the crowd at tomorrow night's carnival.
Dorothy
I'll do you a little favor.
See-through scan mode error.
Switch to normal mode.
Now, please welcome
the heroes who saved the town a year ago!
They are international great detective Jimmy Chen
and genius boy detective Hawxing
and the eccentric security guard Han Jiawei and Inspector Sima
How come someone's missing?
Captain, it's already crunch time,
and you're still attending this ceremony?
I talked it over with the Mayor,
but he thinks we don't have enough evidence.
This is also a high point of the plaza.
We can use this to monitor the scene.
Now, please welcome the Mayor to present the heroes with
the symbol of honorary citizenship of Tuna Town,
sponsored by the Jinmanduo Consortium,
a town key made of solid gold,
the Keys of Hope.
On this special day,
I, on behalf of all the citizens of Tuna Town,
present the Keys of Hope.
To the outstanding fighters who
gave everything to protect the town.
Oh no!
The mechanism is in the statue.
This is...
Uncle!
I'll be taking these keys.
A robot!
My true identity is the Phantom Key Thief, Mardelli.
Collecting town keys is my hobby.
Goodbye, little detective.
Locky
The suspect isn't Dorothy.
It's Chivas and Seagram.
Were we tricked?
Locky
Bomb!
Hawxing
The float
There's a bomb hidden underneath.
The Garden people
and the key thieves are two separate groups.
Locky
There's a bomb under every float!
What?!
Hawxing
I'll help you guys
Shaker, you
Everyone, get down!
The Illumin-Eye
has revived!
You are
This is the true Keys of Hope
You've proven your sincerity to the Eye with your actions. Let's awaken Lord Eye together! Sender: Blue Cross
Hello, everyone
After more than a year
Magic Detective Season 2
is back to meet you all again
Thanks for your support, Magic Fans
Excuse me
Officer Han and Jimmy Chen
Didn't they, at the end of last season,
already get married?
Why is Uncle still single in this episode?
How did Chickenix become
Locky and Jingjing's pet?
Why is Jingjing living at Uncle's place?
That's all for this episode!
Oh really? Then goodbye
How could you forget something so important!
Those times
Always leave you feeling down
Look at tomorrow
On the horizon, it waves to me
Every day is just sunrise and sunset
As time turns, I dream up more
Hoping in this life
Every second, every moment
Bright eyes are shining
A smile that faces the sunlight
Say aloud what you treasure in your heart
That tiny little feeling
Music blows in the morning breeze
Carrying away wishes from all these years
It will quietly wait at the next stop's crossing